myharvestamerica.com 2010-12-21

# My Harvest America

> **PRIVACY USE POLICY**
> 
> The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect from you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct that information.
> 
>   
>  **What Information We Collect and How We Use It**
> 
> Any information we collect on our Site falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information and Aggregate Information.
> 
> **1\. Personally Identifiable Information:** This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. You may, however, voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, e-mail address, and country of origin) for us to contact you, including via e-mail, to respond to your comments or inquiries. In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to provide better service in the event you contact us again.
> 
> **2\. Aggregate Information:** This refers to information that does not by itself identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.  
>  We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.
> 
> **Sharing Your Information**  
>  Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States.  
>  We may share Personally Identifiable Information you provide online with other MYHARVESTAMERICA-related entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate, as well as those that provide services to our Site. Where we engage non-affiliated third-party agents or contractors, we require them to also observe the intent of this Privacy Statement.  
>  From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.  
>  Should MYHARVESTAMERICA or its related entities merge with or be acquired by another business entity, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies serving you and other users of our Site.
> 
> **Accessing and Correcting Your Information**  
>  We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, email support@myharvestamerica.com
> 
> **Protecting Your Information**  
>  We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.
> 
> **Use of Cookies on This Site**  
>  A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you chose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.  
>  Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely.  
>  Our Site may send cookies to your computer's hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site. We Do not, however use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity else where on the web.
> 
> **Use of Third-Party Media and Research Companies**  
>  Our Site does not run non-affiliated third-party ads, nor do we use third-party media and research companies to place ads for us on other parties' Web sites.
> 
> **Links to Other Web Sites**  
>  Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
> 
> **Children's Privacy Protection**  
>  We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data.
> 
> **Changes to This Statement**  
>  Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at that time of use.
> 
> **Contact Us**  
>  If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please email us at [support@myharvestamerica.com](mailto:support@myharvestamerica.com) .
>
>> > > >  

|
